magazineradar.com 2019-06-15

# Privacy Policy - MediaRadar

**MediaRadar Privacy and Cookie Policy  
**  
MediaRadar, Inc., is a Sales Intelligence and Insights platform and technology company. This policy describes the privacy practices that MediaRadar, Inc. (“MediaRadar”, “we”, “us”, “our”) employs relative to data collected and used on our websites and applications that link to this policy, such as [www.mediaradar.com](https://www.mediaradar.com/), [www.adradar.com](http://www.adradar.com/), MediaRadar iPhone App or any other website where this policy is displayed that our clients use.

MediaRadar complies with the EU-U.S. Privacy Shield Framework and the Swiss-U.S. Privacy Shield Framework as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of Personal Data (as defined below) from European Union member countries and Switzerland. We have certified that we adhere to the Privacy Shield Principles of Notice; Choice; Accountability for Onward Transfer; Security; Data Integrity and Purpose Limitation; Access; and Recourse, Enforcement, and Liability. If there is any conflict between the policies in this Privacy Shield Policy and the Privacy Shield Principles, the Privacy Shield Principles shall govern. To learn more about the Privacy Shield program, and to view our certification page, please visit [www.privacyshield.gov](http://www.privacyshield.gov/).

 **Website Visitors and Users**

As a SaaS operator, MediaRadar collects non personally-identifying information typically made available by web browsers and servers, such as browser type, date and time of visit and IP address. This information is collected to measure and improve service quality and is never made available publicly.

MediaRadar collects personally-identifying information (“Personal Information”) when you choose to provide it to us. This may include: name, address, telephone number, or email address. We will use this Personal Information to help us process your registration, fulfill your request, respond to your inquiry, or send you marketing information. We may also be required to disclose Personal Information in response to a lawful request by public or regulatory authorities, including to meet national security or law-enforcement requirements.

People whose Personal Information is covered by this Privacy Policy have the right to access such Personal Information and to correct, amend, or delete it if it is inaccurate or has been processed in violation of the Privacy Shield Principles (except when the burden or expense of providing access, correction, amendment, or deletion would be disproportionate to the risks to the person’s privacy, or where the rights of persons other than the person making the request would be violated). Requests for access, correction, amendment, or deletion should be sent to: [privacy@mediaradar.com](mailto:privacy@mediaradar.com) or to Privacy Official, MediaRadar, 252 W 37th Street, Suite 1001, New York, NY 10018.

 **Cookies**

MediaRadar may store a unique identification number, the username, and login status in a “cookie” on each visitor’s computer. The identification number is retained and utilized to track usage of the web site in order to provide you with products or services you may be interested in, while the username and login status are only used for display purposes and site functionality during your current web session.

In order to change these cookie preferences, you must change your browser’s preferences to disable cookies or delete cookies. Please note that disabling cookies for our services will affect the ability to use those service. Security information is specific to each browser and operating system. Please check with your browser’s specific company for more information.

 **Information Security**

MediaRadar is a multi-tenant SaaS application provider with focus on security at all tiers. We utilize state of the art hosting facilities with software and hardware firewall security and continuous network intrusion detection. Our application is secured from the point of login. All application traffic is SSL encrypted. Data is stored on a firewall-protected database server.

We perform rigorous logging and monitoring at the application level to ensure security and availability of service. Our dedicated operations team, routinely performs pro-active application scans to ensure compliance.

 **Third-party Services**

MediaRadar does not currently share any data with non-agent third parties. If that practice should change in the future we will update this policy and provide individual with opt-out or opt-in choice as required. MediaRadar utilizes Google Analytics to analyze the usage of its websites. For more information on Google Analytics and its privacy policy, please visit <http://www.google.com/analytics/learn/privacy.html>.

MediaRadar may also employ the services of CrazyEgg to collect information about how our site is used. For more information on CrazyEgg and its privacy policy, please visit <https://www.crazyegg.com/privacy>.

Our ad network partners may use cookies and pixels to collect non-personally-identifiable information about your activities on this and other websites to provide you targeted advertising based upon your interests.

Pursuant to the Privacy Shield MediaRadar may be liable for the onward transfer of EU and Swiss personal data unless we can prove we are not responsible for the damages incurred.

Note that MediaRadar may be required to release personal data of EU or Swiss individuals in response to lawful requests by public authorities including to meet National Security and law enforcement requirements.

 **Recourse, Enforcement, and Liability**

MediaRadar’s participation in the EU-U.S. Privacy Shield Framework and the Swiss-U.S. Privacy Shield Framework is subject to investigation and enforcement by the Federal Trade Commission.

In compliance with the Privacy Shield Principles, MediaRadar commits to resolve complaints about your privacy and our collection or use of your Personal Data. Data Subjects with inquiries or complaints regarding this Privacy Shield Policy should first contact MediaRadar at: privacy@mediaradar.com

MediaRadar has further committed to refer unresolved privacy complaints under the EU-U.S. and Swiss-U.S. Privacy Shield Principles to an independent dispute resolution mechanism, the BBB EU PRIVACY SHIELD, operated by the Council of Better Business Bureaus. If you do not receive timely acknowledgment of your complaint, or if your complaint is not satisfactorily addressed, please visit <https://www.bbb.org/EU-privacy-shield/for-eu-consumers> for more information and to file a complaint.

Under certain conditions detailed in the Privacy Shield, Data Subjects may be able to invoke binding arbitration before the Privacy Shield Panel to be created by the U.S. Department of Commerce and the European Commission.  
If you have any questions about our privacy practices, you can send a written request to privacy@mediaradar.com or to Privacy Official, MediaRadar, 252 W 37th Street, Suite 1001, New York, NY 10018.

 **Changes to Privacy and Cookies Policy**

MediaRadar reserves the right to change this Privacy and Cookies Policy without prior notice at any time, and will do so by posting the updated version on our Site.
